<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://boring180.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://boring180.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-04-10T10:36:29+00:00</updated><id>https://boring180.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Borong Xu’s homepage</title><subtitle>My homepage. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Recent Updates</title><link href="https://boring180.github.io/blog/2025/recent-updates/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Recent Updates"/><published>2025-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://boring180.github.io/blog/2025/recent-updates</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://boring180.github.io/blog/2025/recent-updates/"><![CDATA[<p>This is the first year since I joined CPEG(Computer Engineering Program of HKUST), and approximately two years since my first “Hello World” program. I have been through a lot of things in 2024, and I would like to share some of them with you.</p> <p>In the end of 2023, I had a review of my academic life, and I found that I was no longer interested in design and the stress of ISD had ruined my university life. I decided to change my major to something more technical, and I’m currently studying in the Computer Engineering Program of HKUST.</p> <p>I have taken a lot of COMP courses in 2024, and I have released my notes of COMP2011, COMP2012, COMP2611, COMP3711, and COMP 5212. The notes are available on my <a href="https://boring180.github.io/Resources/">resource page</a>.</p> <p>There are various fields in CPEG, and I choose AI and Robotics as my main focus. I will take more courses in these two fields in the future, and hopefully I can contribute to the field of AI and Robotics in the future.</p> <p>To introduce myself in a more detailed way, I made this website in late 2024. I hope you can know more about me through this website, and I will keep updating it in the future.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="essay"/><category term="updates"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updats of my current life & study.]]></summary></entry></feed>